U.S. Agency for International Development Records, Programs, and Itineraries 5384
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Bureau for Near East and South Asia
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Light Metal Fabrication Study Team, Project 277-30226, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Marketing and Sales Study, Project 277-30230, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Industrial and Production Engineering Team, Project 277-30231, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training Cooperatives, PIO/P 277-356-1-60015, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Labor Relations Service, PIO/P 277-397-1-60233, 277-397-1-60234, 277-397-1-60235, 277-397-1-60236, 277-397-1-60237, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training (Organizing, Methods and Structure), PIO/P 277-356-1-60241, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Union Finance and Administration, PIO/P 277-356-1-50240, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Kutay Aksel, PIO/P 277-356-1-70172, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Mediation and Arbitration Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70164, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Worker Education Team #1, PIO/P 277-356-1-70098, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Trade Union Collective Bargaining Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70113, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Turkey: Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 277-356-1-60222, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training - Statistical Research, PIO/P 277-13-410-356-1-40311, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Workers Education Team No. 1, PIO/P 277-356-1-50252, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Workers Education Team No. 2, PIO/P 277-356-1-50252, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Collective Bargaining Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-50235, PIO/P 277-356-1-50236, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Union Finance and Administration Study Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70175, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Turkey: Training in Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 277-364-1-60043, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Organizing and Establishing (I) Local Union, PIO/P 277-356-1-60143, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Mediation, Conciliation, Arbitration and National Labor Relations Board Studies, PIO/P 277-356-1-60193, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Mediation and Voluntary Arbitration Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70162, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Hasan Turkay, PIO/P 277-356-1-70171, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Enver Turgut, PIO/P 277-356-1-79176, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training (Structure, Function and Administration of National Trade Unions Team), PIO/P 277-356-1-70226, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training (Employment Service, Ministry of Labor), PIO/P 277-356-1-60108, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training (Trade Union Organizing Methods and Techniques Team), PIO/P 277-356-1-70225, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Employment Service, Ministry of Labor, PIO/P 277-356-1-60107, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Collective Bargaining & Duties & Functions of Trade Union Officers, PIO/P 277-356-1-60032, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training (Mediation and Arbitration Trade Union Team), PIO/P 277-356-1-70193, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Turkey: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Orhan Alpakin, PIO/P 277-356-1-60223, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Training in Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 277-363-1-50219, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Labor Relations Services, Mediation and Arbitration, Teams I and II, PIO/P 277-397-1-80052/53, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Trade Union Journalism and Communication Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70212, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Trade Union Health and Safety Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70227, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Organizing and Establishing Local Unions, PIO/P 277-356-1-70188, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Turkey: Industrial Relations Training, Women's Role in the Trade Union Movement Team, PIO/P 277-356-1-70207, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Iran: Labor Services and Training, PIO/P 265-11-420-041-1-40111, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Jordan: Industrial Management Study, Project 278-40057, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - India: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - India: Engineering Study Team, Project 386-40188, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - India: Industrial Safety and Hygiene, PIO/P 386-11-450-161-1-40146, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - India: Industrial Safety and Hygiene, PIO/P 386-11-450-161-1-40142, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - India: Industrial Safety and Hygiene, PIO/P 386-11-450-161-1-40151, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Pakistan: Development of Statistical Services, PIO/P 391-037-1-40373, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - India: Employment Services Training, PIO/P 386-50129, 1965-06-02-1965-12-04 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pakistan: Development of Statistical Services (Training in Price Statistics), PIO/P 391-037-1-40494, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - India: Workers Education Training, PIO/P 386-50081, 1965-06-16-1965-12-22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - India: Labor Ministry Training (Labor Administration), PIO/P 386-161-1-60159, 1966-07-31-1966-11-19 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pakistan: Programs and Itineraries (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Labor Relations, PIO/P 391-245-1-60393, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Industrial Relations Training, Anwar M. Hossain, PIO/P 391-245-1-70385, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Industrial Relations Training, Muhammad Mahmood Chaudhri, PIO/P 391-245-1-70541, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Labor Relations Training, Conciliation and Arbitration Team, PIO/P 391-245-1-70377, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Labor-Management Relations Team, PIO/P 391-245-1-60379, 391-245-1-60407, 391-245-1-60386, 391-245-1-60393, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Syed Mahmud Ahmad, PIO/P 391-125-1-40512, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Ministry of Labor, Manpower Statistics Team, PIO/P 391-245-1-70387, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Industrial Relations Training, Mohammad Sabih, M. Aziz Ahmad, and Serajul Huq, PIO/P 391-245-1-70384 and 70463, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Labor Relations Training, Labor Relations Team, PIO/P 391-245-1-70383, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Labor Management Relations, PIO/P 391-125-1-40509, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Foundry Industry Productivity Study Team, Project 391-30489, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pakistan: Employment Services Training, Hamid Hasan Khan, PIO/P 391-245-1-70376, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Jordan: Training in Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 278-083-1-60042, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - India: Labor Administration, PIO/P 386-161-1-60249, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Iran: Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 265-131-1-50081, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pakistan: Programs and Itineraries (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pakistan: Development of Statistical Services, PIO/P 391-037-1-40373, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pakistan: Development of Statistical Services, Training in Price Statistics, PIO/P 391-037-1-40494, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pakistan: Tools, Jigs and Fixtures, Productivity Study Team, Project 391-30490, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cyprus: Kyriacos Polycarpou Demetriades, PIO/P 233-025-1-60017, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - India: Industrial Relations Training, Pangal Manjappa Nayak, PIO/P 386-109-1-70220, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Series IV. Bureau for Latin America and the Caribbean
  - Peru: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Peru: Highway Engineering and Maintenance Study Team, Project 527-40083, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Peru: Highway Engineering Study Team, Project 527-30013, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Peru: Latin American Group XXX Labor Development, PIO/P: 527-063-1-40116, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Peru: Latin American Labor Training Group XXVII, PIO/P 527-063-1-40049, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Team B
    - Peru: Latin American Labor Training Group XXVII, PIO/P 527-063-1-40049, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Peru: Labor Journalists, PIO/P 527-063-1-40051, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Peru: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Peru: Processed Food Industry Study, Project 527-50124, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Peru: Highway Transportation Study, Project 527-50102, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Peru: Latin American Labor Leaders Course, PIO/P 527-AC-41-AC-5-1-30063, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Peru: Highway Engineers Study Team, Project 527-40131, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Peru: Latin American Labor Leaders Course, PIO/P 527-AC-41-AC-5-1-30063, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Team C
  - Ecuador: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ecuador: Labor Training Group XXVI, Project 518-40111, 1963-11-1963-12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ecuador: Highway Equipment Maintenance Study Team Booklets, PIO/P 518-U-40-AA-1-30149, 1964-04-1964-05 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Costa Rica: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica: Area Development Association Study, Project 515-50072, 1965-06-1965-07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica: Small Store Retailing, Project 515-50108, 1965-09-1965-10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica: Small Store Retailing Study, Project 515-40132, 1964-09-1964-10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica: Insurance Agents Study, PIO/P 515-50007, 1964-10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica: Furniture Industry Study, Project 515-40103, 1965-02-1965-03 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Venezuela: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Venezuela: Metal Working Industries Study, Project 529-20109, 1962-10-1962-11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Venezuela: Shoe Manufacture Study Team, Project 529-30253, 1963-07 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Venezuela: Latin American Labor Employment Services, PIO/P 529-013-1-40108, 1964-02-1964-04 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Venezuela: Social Security Training Program, PIO/P 529-N-69-AA-1-30258, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Trinidad and Tobago: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Trinidad and Tobago: Labor-Management-Government Relations, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Trinidad: Labor Training Team, PIO/P 533-N-49-AA-1-20038, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mexico: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mexico: Labor Union Metal Workers Team, PIO/P 523-W-49-AC-1-20059, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mexico: Graphic Arts, Union Cooperative Housing, Project 523-000-1-40014, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chile: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Booklets regarding trade, industry and social security
    - Chile: Metal Workers Trade Union Leadership Team, PIO/P 513-AB-40-AE-5-1-30168, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: White Collar Labor Leaders, 513-W-49-AY-1-20093, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Trade Union Activities Team, PIO/P 513-AB-40-AE-5-1-30085, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Social Security Training Program, PIO/P 513-032-1-40012, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Union Department Leaders, PIO/P 513-AB-40-AE-5-1-30067, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Food Industry Study Team, Project 513-30138, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Latin American Textile Industry, PIO/P 513-032-1-40035, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chile: Latin American Regional Trade Union Leadership, PIO/P 513-032-1-40036, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chile: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Chile: Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 513-AB-40-AE-5-1-30120, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Chile: Latin American Food Workers UITA Trade Union, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Chile: Manpower Surveys and Manpower Training, PIO/P 513-AB-68-AA-5-1-30126, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - British Guiana: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Labor-Management Relations, PIO/P 504-U-41-AA-1-30007, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Trade Union Leadership, 504-41-037-1-20029, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Municipality Labor Training, PIO/P 504-008-1-40008, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Labor and Trade Union Leadership, PIO/P 504-001-1-40024, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Labor and Trade Union Leadership, PIO/P 504-001-1-40026, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Labor and Trade Union Leadership, PIO/P 504-001-1-50001, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - British Guiana: Labor and Trade Union Leadership, PIO/P 504-001-1-40027, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Brazil: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Brazil: Labor Leader-Workers Education Training, PIO/P 512-028-1-50005, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Brazil: Industrial Development Planners Study, Project 512-40253, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Brazil: Mixed Industry Group, 512-U-41-AA-1-20149, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Brazil, Recife: Water Resources and Development Study Team, Project 512-50117, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Brazil: Bank Workers Trade Union Leaders, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Brazil: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Booklets concerning labor and trade unions, and infrastructure study teams
    - Brazil, Porto Alegre: Highway Engineers Study Team, Project 512-40300, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: National Confederation of Commercial Employees, PIO/P 512-028-1-40242, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Warehousemen and Coffee Loaders Team, PIO/P 512-028-1-60048, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Construction Workers Team, PIO/P 512-028-1-60005, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Brazilian Ministry Labor Reorganization Study Mission, PIO/P 512-028-1-50326, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Communication Workers Labor Team, Project 512-50221, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Metal Workers Labor Team, Project 512-50242, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Brazil: Labor Leaders Training & Workers Education, PIO/P 512-028-1-40261, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Brazil: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brazil: Trade Union Journalist Team, PIO/P 512-U-41-AA-1-30078, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brazil: Labor Union Leader Training, Petroleum Worker, PIO/P 512-U-41-AA-1-30138, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brazil: Trade Union Communications Industry Team, PIO/P 512-U-41-AA-1-30190, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brazil: Transportation Workers, PIO/P 512-U-41-AA-1-40018, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brazil: Labor Leaders Training and Workers Education, PIO/P 512-028-1-50001, PIO/P 512-028-1-50002, Team 1 and Team 2, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Two booklets.
  - Brazil: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Geophysical, Photogrammetric and Cartographic Study Team, Project 512-30099, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Highway Directors Study Team, Project 512-40149, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Highway Engineering Study Team, Project 512-40111, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil, Northeast: Highway Engineers Study Team, Project 512-50123, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil, Recife: Water Well Drilling Study Team, Project 512-50119, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil, Rio de Janeiro: Highway Engineers Study Team, Project 512-50062, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Paper & Cardboard Workers Team, Project 512-50210, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Food Workers Labor Team, Project 512-50243, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Electric Power Engineering Study, Project 512-50163, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Brazil: Chemical & Oil Refinery Workers Team, Project 512-50214, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bolivia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Private Bank Employees Trade Union Team, Project 511-40178, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Teachers Trade Union Teams, Projects 511-40179 and 511-40180, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Chauffeurs' Trade Union Team, Project 511-40177, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Petroleum Workers Trade Union Team, Project 511-40181, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Latin American White Collar Unions, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30257, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bolivia: Latin American Textile Worker's Union, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30255, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bolivia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bolivia: Latin American Petroleum Worker's Union, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30254, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bolivia: Latin American Telecommunications Union, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30253, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bolivia: Factory Workers Team, PIO/P 511-043-1-50119, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Honduras: Labor Training and Education in Labor Statistics, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Antigua, West Indies: Labor Training Union Organization and Administration, PIO/P 533-N-49-AA-1-20071, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - St. Lucia, West Indies: Labor Training - Labor Administration and Industrial Relations, PIO/P 533-N-49-AA-1-30019, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - El Salvador: Latin American Trade Union Training Group XXIV, PIO/P 519-U-49-AA-1-20102, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - El Salvador: Latin American Trade Union Training Group XXIV, PIO/P 519-U-49-AA-1-20102, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bolivia, Ecuador, El Salvador, Colombia: The Formation and Flow of Capital, Program No. 7, Group 1, 915-39157, 514-30107, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bolivia, Honduras, India, Nepal, Philippines, Trinidad: The Formation and Flow of Capital, Program No. 7, Group 2, Project 915-39157, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Peru, Uruguay: Latin American Labor Training Group XXVII, PIO/P 527--063-1-40049, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dominican Republic: Industrial Safety and Hygiene, PIO/P 517-U-45-AA-1-30001, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dominican Republic: Labor Training Latin American Group XXV, PIO/P 517-U-45-AB-1-30060, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Colombia: Resources Development Study Team, Project 514-20110, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Colombia, El Salvador, Guatemala, Uruguay: Latin American Labor Training Group XXVIII, PIO/P 515-015-1-40051, PIO/P 519-11-410-003-1-40055, PIO/P 520-146-1-40085, PIO/P 528-010-1-40051, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bolivia, El Salvador, Trinidad: Industrial Development and Management Studies, Productivity & Employment Study Program No. 3 - Groups I & II, PIO/P 915-39153, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bolivia, Peru, Trinidad, Philippines: Industrial Development and Management Studies, Top Management Study Program No. 5, Project 915-39155, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Group 1 and Group 2
  - Peru, Philippines, Nicaragua, Trinidad: Industrial Development and Management Studies, Top Management Study, Program No. 4, Project 915-39154, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Argentina, Colombia: Latin American Labor Training Group XXIX, PIO/P 510-054-1-50017, 514-015-1-40051, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Brazil: Arnaldo da Costa Prieto, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bolivia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia: Latin American Labor Training Group XXVI, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30248, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia: Labor Training - Airline Workers, Team No. 11, Pio/P 511-11-410-043-1-30252, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia: Labor Training - Factory Workers - Labor Relations & Productivity, PIO/P 511-11-410-043-1-30249, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bolivia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia: Labor Training - Miners Union, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-30250, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia: Labor Training - Airline Workers, PIO/P 511-11-410-043-1-30251, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia: Observation in US Labor Organizations, PIO/P 511-11-410-043-1-40044, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia: Teachers Basic Trade Union Program, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-20269, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia: Mine Workers, Basic Trade Union Training, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-20272, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bolivia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bolivia: Bank Employees Trade Union Team, Project 511-043-1-40182, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bolivia: Trade Union Communication Workers Team, PIO/P 511-043-1-40198, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Panama: Training in Manpower Statistics, PIO/P 525-048-1-50017, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Paraguay: Industrial Development Team, Project 526-60050, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chile: Railroad Workers Trade Union Team, PIO/P 513-032-1-50072, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bolivia, Honduras, and Venezuela: Latin American Trade Union Education Course, PIO/P 511-U-41-AA-1-20271, PIO/P 522-U-41-AA-1-20098, PIO/P 529-49-U-AA-1-30006, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Peru: Railroad Workers Trade Union Team, PIO/P 527-063-1-70176, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Venezuela: [Aptitude Test Development] PIO/P 529-013-1-60216 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chile, Guatemala, Honduras, Panama, Peru: Multi-Country Specialized Labor Union Technical Training Team, PIO/P 513-032-1-60038, 520-147-1-60033, 522-007-1-60029, 525-061-1-60038, 527-063-1-60071, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Department of Labor International Technical Assistance Corps (DOLITAC) Staff Papers (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Staff Paper No. 48: Eugene Hood to Dominican Republic, 1967-04-07-1967-08-04 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bolivia, Costa Rica, Greece, Peru, Philippines, Republic of China, Turkey: Industrial Development and Management Studies. Project 915-39156, 1964-03 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - DOLITAC Staff Paper No. 26: Morris B. Wallach Mission to Brazil, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brazil: Labor Judges Team, PIO/P 512-028-1-60003, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brazil: Consumer Expenditure Survey Team, PIO/P 512-028-1-1-80065, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series V. Bureau for Africa
  - DOLITAC Staff Paper No. 27: Kenneth G. Van Auken Mission to Morocco, 1966-10-21-1966-12-17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Liberia: Programs and Itineraries (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Liberia: Urias J. Nelson, PIO/P 669-079-1-50103, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Liberia: Labor and Price Statistics, Project 669-40045, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Libya: Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 670-AA-79-AB-1-30023, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kenya: National Youth Service Leader Observation, PIO/P 615-123-1-50086, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nigeria: Labor and Price Statistics, PIO/P 620-214-1-60110, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Uganda: Norman A. Shalita, PIO/P 617-016-1-70023, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series VI. Training Manuals
  - Conference Leadership: Manual of Instruction, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development
  - Training Materials for the Instruction of Foundry Supervisors or Supervisory Candidates (Box 4, Folder 22)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 2
  - Job Instruction Training manual (Box 4, Folder 22)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 4
  - Job Methods Training Manual (Box 4, Folder 22)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 5
  - Supervisory Development Program (Box 4, Folder 22)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 6
  - Program Development Institute (Box 4, Folder 22)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 7